[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 28, "question": "How are you and the family bearing up since Amy died?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "and", "the", "family", "bearing", "up", "since", "Amy", "died", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "It's been very difficult, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "been", "very", "difficult", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Amy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "Have you been taken aback by the sheer scale of the reaction to her death?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "been", "taken", "aback", "by", "the", "sheer", "scale", "of", "the", "reaction", "to", "her", "death", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "I have.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "How would you describe how you've been feeling since you heard the news?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "describe", "how", "you", "'ve", "been", "feeling", "since", "you", "heard", "the", "news", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "I think all of those.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "all", "of", "those", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "Where were you when you heard the news?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "were", "you", "when", "you", "heard", "the", "news", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "I was in New York.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "in", "New", "York", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "She was on her own?", "question_tokens": ["She", "was", "on", "her", "own", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "She was on her own.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "was", "on", "her", "own", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "What was your reaction immediately?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "reaction", "immediately", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "I -- I had incredible clarity.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "I", "had", "incredible", "clarity", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 105, "question": "Did a part of you expect this call one day?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "a", "part", "of", "you", "expect", "this", "call", "one", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 106, "answer": "No, not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "What about alcohol?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "alcohol", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "Well, alcohol was a different issue.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "alcohol", "was", "a", "different", "issue", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "But do you have any sort of concrete regrets, things you wish you'd done?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "have", "any", "sort", "of", "concrete", "regrets", ",", "things", "you", "wish", "you", "'d", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "No, I really don't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "really", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "Have you had moments in private where you've really lost it about this or have you been able to keep things together?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "had", "moments", "in", "private", "where", "you", "'ve", "really", "lost", "it", "about", "this", "or", "have", "you", "been", "able", "to", "keep", "things", "together", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "I mean, I have moments when I just can't believe what's happened.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "I", "have", "moments", "when", "I", "just", "ca", "n't", "believe", "what", "'s", "happened", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "Do you think she ever really committed to rehab properly or not?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "she", "ever", "really", "committed", "to", "rehab", "properly", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "What was the moment for you when you thought, OK, wow, this is interesting?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "moment", "for", "you", "when", "you", "thought", ",", "OK", ",", "wow", ",", "this", "is", "interesting", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNP", ",", "NN", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "Well, there's so many stories.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "'s", "so", "many", "stories", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sylvia", "Sylvia"]}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "MD", "VB", ":", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 222, "question": "And the irony was that she actually left the Sylvia Young school because she wasn't, in their eyes, performing academically well enough, right?", "question_tokens": ["And", "the", "irony", "was", "that", "she", "actually", "left", "the", "Sylvia", "Young", "school", "because", "she", "was", "n't", ",", "in", "their", "eyes", ",", "performing", "academically", "well", "enough", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 223, "answer": "Well, Sylvia will say -- Sylvia will say that she wasn't expelled, but she was actually expelled.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Sylvia", "will", "say", "--", "Sylvia", "will", "say", "that", "she", "was", "n't", "expelled", ",", "but", "she", "was", "actually", "expelled", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sylvia Young"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sylvia Young", "Tyler James"]}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "When she left Sylvia, what was the moment for you that you realized this little girl of yours was going to be an international star?", "question_tokens": ["When", "she", "left", "Sylvia", ",", "what", "was", "the", "moment", "for", "you", "that", "you", "realized", "this", "little", "girl", "of", "yours", "was", "going", "to", "be", "an", "international", "star", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "We were -- at Sylvia Young, she met a guy called Tyler James, who was a great friend.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "were", "--", "at", "Sylvia", "Young", ",", "she", "met", "a", "guy", "called", "Tyler", "James", ",", "who", "was", "a", "great", "friend", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sylvia"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 238, "question": "You hadn't seen it coming?", "question_tokens": ["You", "had", "n't", "seen", "it", "coming", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "Not really, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "really", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Janice"]}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "Where do you think she'd got that from?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "do", "you", "think", "she", "'d", "got", "that", "from", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "Well, I'd like to say me, of course, but the truth is that Janice, my ex-wife's family, there were professional musicians on that side, too.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'d", "like", "to", "say", "me", ",", "of", "course", ",", "but", "the", "truth", "is", "that", "Janice", ",", "my", "ex-wife", "'s", "family", ",", "there", "were", "professional", "musicians", "on", "that", "side", ",", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "Was that how you saw it?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "that", "how", "you", "saw", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "A force for good in her life?", "question_tokens": ["A", "force", "for", "good", "in", "her", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "An incredible force for good in her life.", "answer_tokens": ["An", "incredible", "force", "for", "good", "in", "her", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "When she first got together with this guy, as her father, what was your immediate reaction when you saw the kind of person that he was?", "question_tokens": ["When", "she", "first", "got", "together", "with", "this", "guy", ",", "as", "her", "father", ",", "what", "was", "your", "immediate", "reaction", "when", "you", "saw", "the", "kind", "of", "person", "that", "he", "was", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "My immediate reaction was that he was a very charming guy.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "immediate", "reaction", "was", "that", "he", "was", "a", "very", "charming", "guy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "So you were suspicious of his motivation, really?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "were", "suspicious", "of", "his", "motivation", ",", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "I was suspicious of his motivation, yes, I was.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "suspicious", "of", "his", "motivation", ",", "yes", ",", "I", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", ",", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "Do you believe that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "Well, I don't know about ecstasy, but cocaine and heroin, yes, I do.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "about", "ecstasy", ",", "but", "cocaine", "and", "heroin", ",", "yes", ",", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "Did you ever confront him?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "confront", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "Oh, frequently, and his family.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "frequently", ",", "and", "his", "family", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "What would you say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "Leave my daughter alone, leave us alone.", "answer_tokens": ["Leave", "my", "daughter", "alone", ",", "leave", "us", "alone", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "Did they not believe that he had got Amy into these hard drugs?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "they", "not", "believe", "that", "he", "had", "got", "Amy", "into", "these", "hard", "drugs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "Do you fear that, you know, you were going to wake up one day with the terrible news that you eventually did, ironically at a time when she was a lot cleaner, but did you fear through that period with Blake that this was all going to end horribly?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "fear", "that", ",", "you", "know", ",", "you", "were", "going", "to", "wake", "up", "one", "day", "with", "the", "terrible", "news", "that", "you", "eventually", "did", ",", "ironically", "at", "a", "time", "when", "she", "was", "a", "lot", "cleaner", ",", "but", "did", "you", "fear", "through", "that", "period", "with", "Blake", "that", "this", "was", "all", "going", "to", "end", "horribly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "Well, yes, I did.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "yes", ",", "I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Blake"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "But of course, Amy, at the time, thought, what's all the fuss about?", "question_tokens": ["But", "of", "course", ",", "Amy", ",", "at", "the", "time", ",", "thought", ",", "what", "'s", "all", "the", "fuss", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "Yes, but she was a headstrong girl.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", "she", "was", "a", "headstrong", "girl", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Amy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "But, you know, I would imagine fabulously successful, very rich, and probably a little part of her was thinking, hey, dad, back off, this is my life, right?", "question_tokens": ["But", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "would", "imagine", "fabulously", "successful", ",", "very", "rich", ",", "and", "probably", "a", "little", "part", "of", "her", "was", "thinking", ",", "hey", ",", "dad", ",", "back", "off", ",", "this", "is", "my", "life", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "RB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "PRP", ",", "VBD", ",", "RB", "IN", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "But he provided the platform for her to take those drugs?", "question_tokens": ["But", "he", "provided", "the", "platform", "for", "her", "to", "take", "those", "drugs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "So I believe.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "I", "believe", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lisa", "Blake", "Blake"]}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "Could you know?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "You could do, but you know, I think I love Lisa, she loved Blake and Blake loved her in his own way.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "could", "do", ",", "but", "you", "know", ",", "I", "think", "I", "love", "Lisa", ",", "she", "loved", "Blake", "and", "Blake", "loved", "her", "in", "his", "own", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 361, "question": "Have you talked to him since she died?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "talked", "to", "him", "since", "she", "died", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "No, I wouldn't talk to him.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "would", "n't", "talk", "to", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "Has he made any attempt to contact you?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "he", "made", "any", "attempt", "to", "contact", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "He says he has, but he hasn't.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "says", "he", "has", ",", "but", "he", "has", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "He hasn't written to you or anything?", "question_tokens": ["He", "has", "n't", "written", "to", "you", "or", "anything", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "What do you say to people who criticize you like that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "people", "who", "criticize", "you", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "That's a fair point.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "fair", "point", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "Did you feel it was a genuine one, or were you still very concerned?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "feel", "it", "was", "a", "genuine", "one", ",", "or", "were", "you", "still", "very", "concerned", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CD", ",", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "Well, I was concerned, but we had, I could draw her on the experiences that we had with the recovery from the drugs.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "was", "concerned", ",", "but", "we", "had", ",", "I", "could", "draw", "her", "on", "the", "experiences", "that", "we", "had", "with", "the", "recovery", "from", "the", "drugs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "Was the Achilles' heel alcohol in the end?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "the", "Achilles", "'", "heel", "alcohol", "in", "the", "end", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "Well, it clearly was.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "clearly", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "But how bad an addiction was that for her after the drugs?", "question_tokens": ["But", "how", "bad", "an", "addiction", "was", "that", "for", "her", "after", "the", "drugs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "Well, alcohol is far more dangerous than drugs are anyway.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "alcohol", "is", "far", "more", "dangerous", "than", "drugs", "are", "anyway", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBG", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "Had she been drinking alone the night she died?", "question_tokens": ["Had", "she", "been", "drinking", "alone", "the", "night", "she", "died", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "VBG", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "She had started drinking, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "had", "started", "drinking", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "Do you know how much she had that night?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "how", "much", "she", "had", "that", "night", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "I have no idea.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "no", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "But it would appear that she had been drinking alcohol?", "question_tokens": ["But", "it", "would", "appear", "that", "she", "had", "been", "drinking", "alcohol", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "There was alcohol in her system, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "was", "alcohol", "in", "her", "system", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "And do you know what actually killed her?", "question_tokens": ["And", "do", "you", "know", "what", "actually", "killed", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "We're still -- we know it's not drugs, but we don't know the official coroner's verdict.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "still", "--", "we", "know", "it", "'s", "not", "drugs", ",", "but", "we", "do", "n't", "know", "the", "official", "coroner", "'s", "verdict", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "Do you have any instinct?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "instinct", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "Well, my instinct is that it's pretty much what the doctor warned us about.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "my", "instinct", "is", "that", "it", "'s", "pretty", "much", "what", "the", "doctor", "warned", "us", "about", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "What happened in Belgrade, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "happened", "in", "Belgrade", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "When the tour was booked, it was booked -- I mean, obviously, these things are booked nine months previously.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "the", "tour", "was", "booked", ",", "it", "was", "booked", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "obviously", ",", "these", "things", "are", "booked", "nine", "months", "previously", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Belgrade"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "Who does it help?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "does", "it", "help", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "Well, it helps disadvantaged children, young adults.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "helps", "disadvantaged", "children", ",", "young", "adults", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "What's the easiest way to do that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "easiest", "way", "to", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "Well, the easiest way is to go on WWW.AmyWinehouseFoundation.Co.UK and donate.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "easiest", "way", "is", "to", "go", "on", "WWW.AmyWinehouseFoundation.Co.UK", "and", "donate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Friday", "Monday"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Blue Note"], "LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "DT", "VBG", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "Either professionally or personally, or both?", "question_tokens": ["Either", "professionally", "or", "personally", ",", "or", "both", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "CC", "RB", ",", "CC", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "Well, the great memories are seeing her on stage for the first time, but my great memories, the last -- I went away on the Friday to New York, as I say, I had a show the following Monday at the Blue Note.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "great", "memories", "are", "seeing", "her", "on", "stage", "for", "the", "first", "time", ",", "but", "my", "great", "memories", ",", "the", "last", "--", "I", "went", "away", "on", "the", "Friday", "to", "New", "York", ",", "as", "I", "say", ",", "I", "had", "a", "show", "the", "following", "Monday", "at", "the", "Blue", "Note", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "I mean, you must miss her terribly, right?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "you", "must", "miss", "her", "terribly", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "We were.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "were", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", ",", "RB", "EX", "MD", "VB", ":", "RB", "RB", "MD", "VB", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "What do you hope her legacy will be, Mitch?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "hope", "her", "legacy", "will", "be", ",", "Mitch", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "Her legacy will be her music, hopefully there will be -- hopefully there will be some more music.", "answer_tokens": ["Her", "legacy", "will", "be", "her", "music", ",", "hopefully", "there", "will", "be", "--", "hopefully", "there", "will", "be", "some", "more", "music", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitch"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "Her foundation is going to help thousands and thousands of children, and what better legacy could you want than that?", "question_tokens": ["Her", "foundation", "is", "going", "to", "help", "thousands", "and", "thousands", "of", "children", ",", "and", "what", "better", "legacy", "could", "you", "want", "than", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "WP", "RBR", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "She was one of the greatest talents I've ever seen.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "was", "one", "of", "the", "greatest", "talents", "I", "'ve", "ever", "seen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", ":", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "What went through your mind?", "question_tokens": ["What", "went", "through", "your", "mind", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "For a moment, I thought it was just too -- a car and a motorcycle on fire until I got to the scene where my wife was already there.", "answer_tokens": ["For", "a", "moment", ",", "I", "thought", "it", "was", "just", "too", "--", "a", "car", "and", "a", "motorcycle", "on", "fire", "until", "I", "got", "to", "the", "scene", "where", "my", "wife", "was", "already", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 611, "question": "When you look back at the video, what do you think now?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "look", "back", "at", "the", "video", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 612, "answer": "At first, when I saw it was a fire, an accident, I didn't think about myself.", "answer_tokens": ["At", "first", ",", "when", "I", "saw", "it", "was", "a", "fire", ",", "an", "accident", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "think", "about", "myself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Brandon"]}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 616, "question": "I mean, do you consider yourselves to be heroes?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "do", "you", "consider", "yourselves", "to", "be", "heroes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 617, "answer": "Um, I don't -- I don't think hero, like, would be like the word to describe the people who were like trying to help lifting the car, or helping the person, I mean Brandon.", "answer_tokens": ["Um", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "hero", ",", "like", ",", "would", "be", "like", "the", "word", "to", "describe", "the", "people", "who", "were", "like", "trying", "to", "help", "lifting", "the", "car", ",", "or", "helping", "the", "person", ",", "I", "mean", "Brandon", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Abbass"], "LOCATION": ["Anvar"]}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 629, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 630, "answer": "James, Anvar, Abbass, I think you are all heroes as well as everyone who helped to that scene.", "answer_tokens": ["James", ",", "Anvar", ",", "Abbass", ",", "I", "think", "you", "are", "all", "heroes", "as", "well", "as", "everyone", "who", "helped", "to", "that", "scene", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Intensive Care Unit"], "LOCATION": ["Salt Lake City", "Logan"]}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 634, "question": "And Tyler, can you tell me, what is Brandon's -- clarify what Brandon's condition is please, Tyler?", "question_tokens": ["And", "Tyler", ",", "can", "you", "tell", "me", ",", "what", "is", "Brandon", "'s", "--", "clarify", "what", "Brandon", "'s", "condition", "is", "please", ",", "Tyler", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "POS", ":", "NN", "WP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 635, "answer": "He is still in the Intensive Care Unit at a hospital in Salt Lake City, which is about 90 miles south of Logan, but they are hoping to move him out of that unit later today and move him into a regular patient room, where they will upgrade him to the condition of satisfactory.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "is", "still", "in", "the", "Intensive", "Care", "Unit", "at", "a", "hospital", "in", "Salt", "Lake", "City", ",", "which", "is", "about", "90", "miles", "south", "of", "Logan", ",", "but", "they", "are", "hoping", "to", "move", "him", "out", "of", "that", "unit", "later", "today", "and", "move", "him", "into", "a", "regular", "patient", "room", ",", "where", "they", "will", "upgrade", "him", "to", "the", "condition", "of", "satisfactory", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tyler", "Brandon", "Brandon", "Tyler"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", ":", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 642, "question": "Is he aware of the video?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "aware", "of", "the", "video", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 643, "answer": "He has actually did see the video earlier today during some news coverage, and he -- that was the first time that he had seen it, and he was shocked by it.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "has", "actually", "did", "see", "the", "video", "earlier", "today", "during", "some", "news", "coverage", ",", "and", "he", "--", "that", "was", "the", "first", "time", "that", "he", "had", "seen", "it", ",", "and", "he", "was", "shocked", "by", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 647, "question": "And what was -- what was his view, do you think, of the people that saved his life?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "was", "--", "what", "was", "his", "view", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "of", "the", "people", "that", "saved", "his", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", ":", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "I think that he thinks that they were all -- they were all heroes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "he", "thinks", "that", "they", "were", "all", "--", "they", "were", "all", "heroes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 653, "question": "What is your reaction?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 654, "answer": "I'm not kind of surprise.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "kind", "of", "surprise", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]